[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 6 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "71",
      "options": [
        "76",
        "71",
        "73",
        "69"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 1 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "29",
      "options": [
        "27",
        "29",
        "31",
        "34"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 2 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "9",
        "14",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 9 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "59",
      "options": [
        "57",
        "59",
        "61",
        "64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 5 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "20",
        "13",
        "17",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 7 + 2 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "14",
        "11",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 12 + 5 \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "27",
      "options": [
        "27",
        "32",
        "25",
        "29"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 2 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "19",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "19",
        "21",
        "17"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 1 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "10",
        "14",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 5 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "46",
      "options": [
        "51",
        "44",
        "48",
        "46"
      ]
    }
]